U.S. Emergency Board No. 137 Transcript of Proceedings and Exhibits 5057
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Emergency Board No. 137 Transcript of Proceedings and Exhibits
1937-1961
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Emergency Board
5057
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Transcript of proceedings and exhibits of the Emergency Board No. 137, 1961. Wage and benefits case. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, et al. and Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1937-1961.
3114930
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, August 10, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Sources; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States -- Sources; United States. Emergency Board No. 137; Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company--Sources.; Railroad Yardmasters of America--Sources.
3114930
- Report to the President by the Emergency Board, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Wage and Rules Case, Railroad Yardmasters of America Exhibit 1, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Wage and Rules Case, Railroad Yardmasters of America Exhibit 2, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Wage and Rules Case, Railroad Yardmasters of America Exhibit 3, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Wage and Rules Case, Railroad Yardmasters of America Exhibit 4, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Examples of Four-Week Vacations - Union Transit Companies, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Wage and Rules Case, Railroad Yardmasters of America Exhibit 6, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Wage and Rules Case, Railroad Yardmasters of America Exhibit 7, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Wage and Rules Case, Railroad Yardmasters of America Exhibit 8, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Wage and Rules Case, Railroad Yardmasters of America Exhibit 9, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Yardmasters' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case, Carriers Exhibit No. 1, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Yardmasters' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case, Carriers Exhibit No. 3, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Yardmasters' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case, Carriers Exhibit No. 4, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Yardmasters' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case, Carriers Exhibit No. 5, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Yardmasters' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case, Carriers Exhibit No. 6, 1937-1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Yardmasters' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case, Carriers Exhibit No. 7, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Yardmasters' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case, Carriers Exhibit No. 8-A, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Yardmasters' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case, Carriers Exhibit No. 9, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Yardmasters' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case, Carriers Exhibit No. 10, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Yardmasters' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case, Carriers Exhibit No. 11, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Wages and Rules Case - Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Railroad Yardmasters of America Emergency Board No. 137, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Railway Company -and- Railroad Yardmasters of America Emergency Board No. 137 Volume No. 2, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Railway Company -and- Railroad Yardmasters of America Emergency Board No. 137 Volume No. 3, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Railway Company -and- Railroad Yardmasters of America Emergency Board No. 137 Volume No. 5, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Railway Company -and- Railroad Yardmasters of America Emergency Board No. 137 Volume No. 6, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Railway Company -and- Railroad Yardmasters of America Emergency Board No. 137 Volume No. 7, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Railway Company -and- Railroad Yardmasters of America Emergency Board No. 137 Volume No. 8, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Railway Company -and- Railroad Yardmasters of America Emergency Board No. 137 Volume 9, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Railway Company -and- Railroad Yardmasters of America Emergency Board No. 137 Volume No. 10, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Railway Company -and- Railroad Yardmasters of America Emergency Board No. 137 Volume No. 11, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 31)